"世界を舞台に数々の金字塔を打ち立ててきた、Maydayが、この夏、日本にて、新たなる歴史的第一歩を踏み出す。
8月28日・29日、日本の音楽の聖地「日本武道館」での2Days公演の開催が決定したことをバンド結成記念日の3月29日に発表した。
ビートルズやエリック・クラプトンなど彼らが敬愛する世界的スーパースターが立ったステージと同じ舞台に立てることが今回決まり、メンバー5人は以前からの念願だったこの公演を全力で成功させると誓いつつ、初日公演は「DO YOU EVER SHINE」、最終日公演は「抱きしめて」というサブタイトルを付け2日間異なった魅力を持つサプライズ満載の公演にし、全てのオーディエンスにずっと忘れられないような感動と想い出を残したい！と強く願っている。
また、メンバー5人は、世界各国で「Maydayのコンサートは僕らMaydayだけではなく、会場に来てくれる一人一人と共に創り上げるものだから、Maydayに参加するのは、決して遅くはない！」とコメントしており、「今回の日本武道館公演も、全世界のファンと共に伝説的なコンサートを創り上げたい！」ともコメントしている。
そして、そのコメントにもあるように、今回の武道館公演の開催は、彼らが日本で本格的な活動をスタートした意味合いと全く同じものがあり、「国境や言語の壁を越えた一つのアジアを創り出したい」という意味が込められている。
 於世界各地舞台立下多數演出金字塔的亞洲天團，在這個夏天，將會於日本踏出嶄新歷史的第一步。
在成軍紀念日的3月29日發表了8月28日・29日的這2天、正式確定會在日本的音楽聖地「日本武道館」舉辦2Days的演唱會。
確定會繼披頭四，艾力克克萊普頓等他們敬愛的國際巨星之後站上同一個舞台這件事，讓團員5人不但決心要全力以赴使這次夢想實現的演唱會成功，也決定2天的演唱會要展現充滿不同魅力且驚喜滿載的演出，8/28以「DO YOU EVER SHINE」命名，8/29以「抱きしめて」命名，希望可以讓所有的粉絲都留下永難忘懷的感動及回憶！
五月天5人在世界各地最常跟歌迷說的就是：「五月天的演唱會不只是五月天演唱會，還加上來到會場的每一個你們才能創造的，加入五月天，永遠不會太遲！」，也提到「希望這次的日本武道館演唱會，也可以成為與全世界歌迷一起創造傳說的演唱會！」
此外，如同團員的感想中說到，這次武道館演唱會的舉辦，也包含了他們在日本正式開始活動時所期待的「希望可以超越國界及語言的隔閡讓亞洲融為一體」的想法。
 於世界各地舞台立下多数演出金字塔的亚洲天团，在这个夏天，将会於日本踏出崭新歷史的第一步。 在成军纪念日的3月29日发表了8月28日・29日的这2天、正式确定会在日本的音楽圣地「日本武道馆」举办2Days的演唱会。 确定会继披头四，艾力克克莱普顿等他们敬爱的国际巨星之后站上同一个舞台这件事，让团员5人不但决心要全力以赴使这次梦想实现的演唱会成功，也决定2天的演唱会要展现充满不同魅力且惊喜满载的演出，8/28以「DO YOU EVER SHINE」命名，8/29以「抱きしめて」命名，希望可以让所有的粉丝都留下永难忘怀的感动及回忆！ 五月天5人在世界各地最常跟歌迷说的就是：「五月天的演唱会不只是五月天演唱会，还加上来到会场的每一个你们才能创造的，加入五月天，永远不会太迟！」，也提到「希望这次的日本武道馆演唱会，也可以成為与全世界歌迷一起创造传说的演唱会！」 此外，如同团员的感想中说到，这次武道馆演唱会的举办，也包含了他们在日本正式开始活动时所期待的「希望可以超越国界及语言的隔阂让亚洲融為一体」的想法。  Mayday who has hit many milestones across the international stage will take a new history-making step in Japan this summer.
They are confirmed for a two day show on August 28 and 29 at the sacred venue of music – the Nippon Budokan. This was announced on March 29, the anniversary date of forming their band, Mayday.
Mayday will be performing at the venue where all the international superstars they respect have performed such as The Beatles and Eric Clapton. Each member of Mayday has sworn to make these concerts successful to the fullest. These two day performances will have different themes with attractions filled with surprises – the first day is ~DO YOU EVER SHINE~ and the last day is ~Dakishimete~ – they strongly hope to deliver unforgettable inspirations and memories for all the audience members.
Also, five members of Mayday have commented “The concerts of Mayday are created not only by us but also with everyone who comes to our venues so it is never too late to join Mayday!” For the fans overseas, they also comment, “We want to create legendary shows at the Nippon Budokan with fans from all over the world!”
Moreover, performing at the Nippon Budokan is significant because there is an underlying meaning that they have started full-scale activities in Japan. It carries a meaning of “wishing to create one Asia beyond borders and language barriers.
 세계를 무대로 수 많은 금자탑을 세워 온 아시아의 슈퍼 밴드Mayday가 이 번 여름, 일본에서 새로이 역사적 발걸음을 내딛는다.
8월28일・29일, 일본 음악의 성지「일본 부도칸」에서 2Days공연 개최가 결정되었다고, 밴드 결성 기념일인 3월 29일에 발표했다. 

비틀즈, 에릭 클랩튼 등, 그들이 존경하는 세계적인 슈퍼스타가 섰던 무대에 자신들도 같은 무대에 선다는 것이 이번에 결정 되어, 멤버 5명은 예전부터 염원했던 부도칸 공연을 전력을 다해 성공시키겠다고 맹세하며, 첫날 공연은 「〜DO YOU EVER SHINE〜 」마지막날 공연은「〜抱きしめて（다키시메테）〜」라는 서브타이틀을 붙여, 2일간 다른 매력을 가진 서프라이즈가 가득한 공연으로 하여, 모든 관객에게 영원히 잊을 수 없는 감동과 추억을 남겨주고 싶다！는 강한 의지를 보여주고 있다. 

또한 Mayday의 멤버 5 명은 세계 각국에서 「Mayday 콘서트는 우리 뿐만 아니라 공연장에 와주는 관객과 함께 만드는 것이기에 Mayday에 참여하는 것은 결코 늦지 않다!」라는 코멘트를 남기고, 「이번 일본 무도관 공연도 전세계 팬들과 함께 전설적인 콘서트를 만들어주고 싶다!」라고 전했다.  ※車椅子にてご来場のお客様は事前にご連絡ください。
※客席を含む会場内の映像写真が公開されることがありますので予めご了承ください。
※営利目的での転売行為一切禁止/転売チケット入場不可
 ※以輪椅來場的觀眾還請先行告知
※會場內含觀眾席部分的影像有攝影播放的可能性還請理解
※禁止一切以營利為目的所進行的票券轉賣行為／轉賣票券禁止入場
 ※以轮椅来场的观眾还请先行告知
※会场内含观眾席部分的影像有摄影播放的可能性还请理解
※禁止一切以营利為目的所进行的票券转卖行為／转卖票券禁止入场
 *Please contact the organizer in advance if you attend in a wheelchair.
*Please note that videos and images of the shows including audiences might be released to public.
*Resale of tickets and admission with those tickets are prohibited.
 ※휠체어로 입장하실 고객분은 사전에 문의 해 주세요.
※객석을 포함 공연장의 영상,사진이 공개 될수 있으므로 양해 바랍니다.
※영리 목적으로 전매 행위는 절대 금지 / 재매 티켓 입장 불가
 受付終了いたしました。たくさんのご応募ありがとうございました。因為申請的張數眾多，門票已經完售。感謝大家踴躍的購買。 因為申请的张数眾多，门票已经完售。感谢大家踊跃的购买。 We have reached the allotted tickets for Rakuten ticket board and they are no longer available.
Thank you for contacting us. 예정된 티켓수량에 도달하여 티켓예약이 종료되었습니다.
여러분의 많은 응모 해 주셔서 감사합니다. 因為申請的張數眾多，門票已經完售。感謝大家踴躍的購買。 因為申请的张数眾多，门票已经完售。感谢大家踊跃的购买。 We have reached the allotted tickets for Rakuten ticket board and they are no longer available.
Thank you for contacting us. 예정된 티켓수량에 도달하여 티켓예약이 종료되었습니다.
여러분의 많은 응모 해 주셔서 감사합니다. 受付終了いたしました。たくさんのご応募ありがとうございました。 受付終了いたしました。
当落確認・入金期間についてはツアー詳細にてご確認下さいませ。 已經截止。關於抽選結果，匯款期限等情報請於Tour詳細內容部分確認。 已经截止。关於抽选结果，匯款期限等情报请於Tour详细内容部分确认。 Time limit for application expired.
Please refer to the “tour details” for next procedure 접수 종료했습니다. 당첨 확인 · 입금 기간은 투어 상세내용에서 확인해 주시기 바랍니다. Mayday Official Site  
（C）AMUSE Inc. & B’in MUSIC Inc. All Rights Reserved. イントロダクション演唱會簡介演唱会简介IntroductionIntroduction世界を舞台に数々の金字塔を打ち立ててきた、Maydayが、この夏、日本にて、新たなる歴史的第一歩を踏み出す。
8月28日・29日、日本の音楽の聖地「日本武道館」での2Days公演の開催が決定したことをバンド結成記念日の3月29日に発表した。
ビートルズやエリック・クラプトンなど彼らが敬愛する世界的スーパースターが立ったステージと同じ舞台に立てることが今回決まり、メンバー5人は以前からの念願だったこの公演を全力で成功させると誓いつつ、初日公演は「DO YOU EVER SHINE」、最終日公演は「抱きしめて」というサブタイトルを付け2日間異なった魅力を持つサプライズ満載の公演にし、全てのオーディエンスにずっと忘れられないような感動と想い出を残したい！と強く願っている。
また、メンバー5人は、世界各国で「Maydayのコンサートは僕らMaydayだけではなく、会場に来てくれる一人一人と共に創り上げるものだから、Maydayに参加するのは、決して遅くはない！」とコメントしており、「今回の日本武道館公演も、全世界のファンと共に伝説的なコンサートを創り上げたい！」ともコメントしている。
そして、そのコメントにもあるように、今回の武道館公演の開催は、彼らが日本で本格的な活動をスタートした意味合いと全く同じものがあり、「国境や言語の壁を越えた一つのアジアを創り出したい」という意味が込められている。 於世界各地舞台立下多數演出金字塔的亞洲天團，在這個夏天，將會於日本踏出嶄新歷史的第一步。
在成軍紀念日的3月29日發表了8月28日・29日的這2天、正式確定會在日本的音楽聖地「日本武道館」舉辦2Days的演唱會。
確定會繼披頭四，艾力克克萊普頓等他們敬愛的國際巨星之後站上同一個舞台這件事，讓團員5人不但決心要全力以赴使這次夢想實現的演唱會成功，也決定2天的演唱會要展現充滿不同魅力且驚喜滿載的演出，8/28以「DO YOU EVER SHINE」命名，8/29以「抱きしめて」命名，希望可以讓所有的粉絲都留下永難忘懷的感動及回憶！
五月天5人在世界各地最常跟歌迷說的就是：「五月天的演唱會不只是五月天演唱會，還加上來到會場的每一個你們才能創造的，加入五月天，永遠不會太遲！」，也提到「希望這次的日本武道館演唱會，也可以成為與全世界歌迷一起創造傳說的演唱會！」
此外，如同團員的感想中說到，這次武道館演唱會的舉辦，也包含了他們在日本正式開始活動時所期待的「希望可以超越國界及語言的隔閡讓亞洲融為一體」的想法。 於世界各地舞台立下多数演出金字塔的亚洲天团，在这个夏天，将会於日本踏出崭新歷史的第一步。 在成军纪念日的3月29日发表了8月28日・29日的这2天、正式确定会在日本的音楽圣地「日本武道馆」举办2Days的演唱会。 确定会继披头四，艾力克克莱普顿等他们敬爱的国际巨星之后站上同一个舞台这件事，让团员5人不但决心要全力以赴使这次梦想实现的演唱会成功，也决定2天的演唱会要展现充满不同魅力且惊喜满载的演出，8/28以「DO YOU EVER SHINE」命名，8/29以「抱きしめて」命名，希望可以让所有的粉丝都留下永难忘怀的感动及回忆！ 五月天5人在世界各地最常跟歌迷说的就是：「五月天的演唱会不只是五月天演唱会，还加上来到会场的每一个你们才能创造的，加入五月天，永远不会太迟！」，也提到「希望这次的日本武道馆演唱会，也可以成為与全世界歌迷一起创造传说的演唱会！」 此外，如同团员的感想中说到，这次武道馆演唱会的举办，也包含了他们在日本正式开始活动时所期待的「希望可以超越国界及语言的隔阂让亚洲融為一体」的想法。 Mayday who has hit many milestones across the international stage will take a new history-making step in Japan this summer.
They are confirmed for a two day show on August 28 and 29 at the sacred venue of music – the Nippon Budokan. This was announced on March 29, the anniversary date of forming their band, Mayday.
Mayday will be performing at the venue where all the international superstars they respect have performed such as The Beatles and Eric Clapton. Each member of Mayday has sworn to make these concerts successful to the fullest. These two day performances will have different themes with attractions filled with surprises – the first day is ~DO YOU EVER SHINE~ and the last day is ~Dakishimete~ – they strongly hope to deliver unforgettable inspirations and memories for all the audience members.
Also, five members of Mayday have commented “The concerts of Mayday are created not only by us but also with everyone who comes to our venues so it is never too late to join Mayday!” For the fans overseas, they also comment, “We want to create legendary shows at the Nippon Budokan with fans from all over the world!”
Moreover, performing at the Nippon Budokan is significant because there is an underlying meaning that they have started full-scale activities in Japan. It carries a meaning of “wishing to create one Asia beyond borders and language barriers.세계를 무대로 수 많은 금자탑을 세워 온 아시아의 슈퍼 밴드Mayday가 이 번 여름, 일본에서 새로이 역사적 발걸음을 내딛는다.
8월28일・29일, 일본 음악의 성지「일본 부도칸」에서 2Days공연 개최가 결정되었다고, 밴드 결성 기념일인 3월 29일에 발표했다. 

비틀즈, 에릭 클랩튼 등, 그들이 존경하는 세계적인 슈퍼스타가 섰던 무대에 자신들도 같은 무대에 선다는 것이 이번에 결정 되어, 멤버 5명은 예전부터 염원했던 부도칸 공연을 전력을 다해 성공시키겠다고 맹세하며, 첫날 공연은 「〜DO YOU EVER SHINE〜 」마지막날 공연은「〜抱きしめて（다키시메테）〜」라는 서브타이틀을 붙여, 2일간 다른 매력을 가진 서프라이즈가 가득한 공연으로 하여, 모든 관객에게 영원히 잊을 수 없는 감동과 추억을 남겨주고 싶다！는 강한 의지를 보여주고 있다. 

또한 Mayday의 멤버 5 명은 세계 각국에서 「Mayday 콘서트는 우리 뿐만 아니라 공연장에 와주는 관객과 함께 만드는 것이기에 Mayday에 참여하는 것은 결코 늦지 않다!」라는 코멘트를 남기고, 「이번 일본 무도관 공연도 전세계 팬들과 함께 전설적인 콘서트를 만들어주고 싶다!」라고 전했다. メンバーコメント團員感想团员感想Comments from Members멤버 코멘트ASHIN（阿信）【Vo.】

Maydayの代表曲はもちろん、日本語で歌う楽曲も沢山用意していくから、日本の皆さんにも楽しんでもらえるコンサートになると思います。そして遠くから来てくれるファンの期待も裏切らないコンサートにして、アジア中のファンが一体になるような貴重な瞬間を生み出す事こそが、僕らにとっての一番の願いです。Maydayの代表曲はもちろん、日本語で歌う楽曲も沢山用意していくから、日本の皆さんにも楽しんでもらえるコンサートになると思います。そして遠くから来てくれるファンの期待も裏切らないコンサートにして、アジア中のファンが一体になるような貴重な瞬間を生み出す事こそが、僕らにとっての一番の願いです。阿信【Vo.】

除了Mayday的代表曲目之外，當然也會演唱許多日文的歌曲，希望會是讓日本的歌迷們都開心的演唱會。不過當然也不會辜負自遠方而來的歌迷的期待。在演唱會中發生讓亞洲歌迷融為一體的瞬間，是我們最期望的事。除了Mayday的代表曲目之外，當然也會演唱許多日文的歌曲，希望會是讓日本的歌迷們都開心的演唱會。不過當然也不會辜負自遠方而來的歌迷的期待。在演唱會中發生讓亞洲歌迷融為一體的瞬間，是我們最期望的事。阿信【Vo.】

除了Mayday的代表曲目之外，当然也会演唱许多日文的歌曲，希望会是让日本的歌迷们都开心的演唱会。不过当然也不会辜负自远方而来的歌迷的期待。在演唱会中发生让亚洲歌迷融為一体的瞬间，是我们最期望的事。除了Mayday的代表曲目之外，当然也会演唱许多日文的歌曲，希望会是让日本的歌迷们都开心的演唱会。不过当然也不会辜负自远方而来的歌迷的期待。在演唱会中发生让亚洲歌迷融為一体的瞬间，是我们最期望的事。ASHIN [Vocal]

I will prepare to sing not only popular songs of Mayday but also many others in Japanese so that this will be a show that Japanese fans can enjoy too. We also make sure not to betray expectations of fans who come from far away. Our biggest hope is to produce a precious moment where all the fans from Asia can be one.I will prepare to sing not only popular songs of Mayday but also many others in Japanese so that this will be a show that Japanese fans can enjoy too. We also make sure not to betray expectations of fans who come from far away. Our biggest hope is to produce a precious moment where all the fans from Asia can be one.ASHIN（阿信）【Vo.】

Mayday의 대표곡은 물론 일본어로 부르는 곡도 많이 준비하고 있어, 일본 여러분들에게도 즐거운 콘서트가 되리라 생각합니다. 그리고 멀리서 와주신 팬들의 기대에도 부응할 수 있는 콘서트로 하여 아시아 전체의 팬들이 하나가 되는 귀중한 순간을 만들어 내는 것이야 말로 우리에게 있어서 가장 큰 바람입니다. Mayday의 대표곡은 물론 일본어로 부르는 곡도 많이 준비하고 있어, 일본 여러분들에게도 즐거운 콘서트가 되리라 생각합니다. 그리고 멀리서 와주신 팬들의 기대에도 부응할 수 있는 콘서트로 하여 아시아 전체의 팬들이 하나가 되는 귀중한 순간을 만들어 내는 것이야 말로 우리에게 있어서 가장 큰 바람입니다. MONSTER（怪獸）【Gt.】

親友である日本のミュージシャン達も来てくれるそうなので、この記念すべきコンサートを彼らと共に見届けて欲しいと思います。そして6月リリースのシングルに「ナインボール」が収録！これは僕が主演した映画の主題歌なんですが、この曲は阿信と共にダブルボーカルで日本語歌唱をする予定なのでニューシングルも是非楽しみにしていて下さい。親友である日本のミュージシャン達も来てくれるそうなので、この記念すべきコンサートを彼らと共に見届けて欲しいと思います。そして6月リリースのシングルに「ナインボール」が収録！これは僕が主演した映画の主題歌なんですが、この曲は阿信と共にダブルボーカルで日本語歌唱をする予定なのでニューシングルも是非楽しみにしていて下さい。怪獸【Gt.】

聽說日本的音樂人超級好朋友們也都會來，希望他們可以共同見證這場值得紀念的演唱會。而６月份發行的新單曲裡將會收錄「九號球」！這是我所主演的電影主題曲，會和阿信一起用日文演唱這首歌，希望大家也可以喜歡這首單曲。聽說日本的音樂人超級好朋友們也都會來，希望他們可以共同見證這場值得紀念的演唱會。而６月份發行的新單曲裡將會收錄「九號球」！這是我所主演的電影主題曲，會和阿信一起用日文演唱這首歌，希望大家也可以喜歡這首單曲。怪兽【Gt.】

听说日本的音乐人超级好朋友们也都会来，希望他们可以共同见证这场值得纪念的演唱会。而６月份发行的新单曲裡将会收录「九号球」！这是我所主演的电影主题曲，会和阿信一起用日文演唱这首歌，希望大家也可以喜欢这首单曲。听说日本的音乐人超级好朋友们也都会来，希望他们可以共同见证这场值得纪念的演唱会。而６月份发行的新单曲裡将会收录「九号球」！这是我所主演的电影主题曲，会和阿信一起用日文演唱这首歌，希望大家也可以喜欢这首单曲。MONSTER [Guitar]

My Japanese musician friends are coming to see the shows as well so I want you all to witness this memorable concert with them. And the new single that will be released in June includes Nine Ball! This is the theme song for the film I starred in and this will be sung by both Ashin and me in Japanese so we hope you like the new single.My Japanese musician friends are coming to see the shows as well so I want you all to witness this memorable concert with them. And the new single that will be released in June includes Nine Ball! This is the theme song for the film I starred in and this will be sung by both Ashin and me in Japanese so we hope you like the new single.MONSTER（怪獸）【Gt.】

절친인 일본 뮤지션들도 와주신다고 하여 이 특별한 콘서트를 그들과 함께 끝까지 봐주셨으면 합니다. 그리고 6월에 발매될 싱글에「나인볼」도 수록！ 이것은 제가 주연한 영화의 주제가인데 이 곡은 아신과 함께 더블 보컬로 일본어로 부를 예정이니 뉴 싱글도 기대해 주세요. 절친인 일본 뮤지션들도 와주신다고 하여 이 특별한 콘서트를 그들과 함께 끝까지 봐주셨으면 합니다. 그리고 6월에 발매될 싱글에「나인볼」도 수록！ 이것은 제가 주연한 영화의 주제가인데 이 곡은 아신과 함께 더블 보컬로 일본어로 부를 예정이니 뉴 싱글도 기대해 주세요. STONE（石頭）【Gt.】

以前、日本武道館でエリック・クラプトンのコンサートを見たことがあるのですが、まさかこんなに早く自分が武道館のステージに立って、ギターを弾くことが出来るとは思っていなかったです。8月はMaydayと一緒になって、みんなで武道館をライブハウスに変えましょう！以前、日本武道館でエリック・クラプトンのコンサートを見たことがあるのですが、まさかこんなに早く自分が武道館のステージに立って、ギターを弾くことが出来るとは思っていなかったです。8月はMaydayと一緒になって、みんなで武道館をライブハウスに変えましょう！石頭【Gt.】

以前到日本武道館看過艾立克克萊普頓的演唱會，沒想到自己這麼快就能站在武道館的舞台上彈吉他。希望８月的時候大家可以和五月天一起，把武道館變成Live House！以前到日本武道館看過艾立克克萊普頓的演唱會，沒想到自己這麼快就能站在武道館的舞台上彈吉他。希望８月的時候大家可以和五月天一起，把武道館變成Live House！石头【Gt.】

以前到日本武道馆看过艾立克克莱普顿的演唱会，没想到自己这麼快就能站在武道馆的舞台上弹吉他。希望８月的时候大家可以和五月天一起，把武道馆变成Live House！以前到日本武道馆看过艾立克克莱普顿的演唱会，没想到自己这麼快就能站在武道馆的舞台上弹吉他。希望８月的时候大家可以和五月天一起，把武道馆变成Live House！STONE [Guitar]

I have been at the Nippon Budokan to watch Eric Clapton’s concert but I never imagined myself standing there and playing guitar this early in my life. Let’s get together with Mayday in August and change the Budokan to a concert venue!I have been at the Nippon Budokan to watch Eric Clapton’s concert but I never imagined myself standing there and playing guitar this early in my life. Let’s get together with Mayday in August and change the Budokan to a concert venue!STONE（石頭）【Gt.】

예전에 일본 부도칸에서 에릭 클랩튼의 콘서트를 본 적이 있는데 설마 이렇게 빨리 내 자신이 부도칸 대에 서서 기타를 치게 될 줄은 생각도 못했습니다. 8월은 Mayday와 하나가 되어 다 같이 부도칸을 라이브하우스로 바꿔 봅시다！예전에 일본 부도칸에서 에릭 클랩튼의 콘서트를 본 적이 있는데 설마 이렇게 빨리 내 자신이 부도칸 대에 서서 기타를 치게 될 줄은 생각도 못했습니다. 8월은 Mayday와 하나가 되어 다 같이 부도칸을 라이브하우스로 바꿔 봅시다！MASA（瑪莎）【Ba.】

最近の僕らのコンサートでは、巨大なロボット象が突如出現するのですが、東京までその専用ロボット象を僕のスーツケースに入れて持っていきたいと思っています！最近の僕らのコンサートでは、巨大なロボット象が突如出現するのですが、東京までその専用ロボット象を僕のスーツケースに入れて持っていきたいと思っています！瑪莎【Ba.】

最近我們的演唱會有一隻巨大的機器大象會突然出現在舞台上，希望我的行李箱能裝得下那隻專屬的機器大象運到東京！最近我們的演唱會有一隻巨大的機器大象會突然出現在舞台上，希望我的行李箱能裝得下那隻專屬的機器大象運到東京！玛莎【Ba.】

最近我们的演唱会有一隻巨大的机器大象会突然出现在舞台上，希望我的行李箱能装得下那隻专属的机器大象运到东京！最近我们的演唱会有一隻巨大的机器大象会突然出现在舞台上，希望我的行李箱能装得下那隻专属的机器大象运到东京！MASA [Bass]

A gigantic elephant robot has been appearing suddenly at our recent shows and I plan to put the elephant robot in my suitcase and bring it to Japan!A gigantic elephant robot has been appearing suddenly at our recent shows and I plan to put the elephant robot in my suitcase and bring it to Japan!MASA（瑪莎）【Ba.】

최근, 저희 콘서트에서는 거대한 로봇상이 갑자기 출현하는데요. 도쿄까지 그 전용 로봇상을 제 여행가방에 넣어 가고 싶어요！최근, 저희 콘서트에서는 거대한 로봇상이 갑자기 출현하는데요. 도쿄까지 그 전용 로봇상을 제 여행가방에 넣어 가고 싶어요！MING（冠佑）【Dr.】

ずっと念願だった日本武道館でのコンサートが決まりとても嬉しく思っています。そして、連続2日間の2Days公演なので、打ち上げ会場を「つけ麺」と「焼き肉」のどっちにするかを選ぶ苦痛から脱出できることも嬉しく思っています（笑）ずっと念願だった日本武道館でのコンサートが決まりとても嬉しく思っています。そして、連続2日間の2Days公演なので、打ち上げ会場を「つけ麺」と「焼き肉」のどっちにするかを選ぶ苦痛から脱出できることも嬉しく思っています（笑）冠佑【Dr.】

真的很高興可以登上一直期待的日本武道館辦演唱會。
而連續兩天的兩場演出，慶功宴會場可以不必在沾麵與燒肉兩者間做痛苦的抉擇，各安排一天就可以了！（笑）真的很高興可以登上一直期待的日本武道館辦演唱會。
而連續兩天的兩場演出，慶功宴會場可以不必在沾麵與燒肉兩者間做痛苦的抉擇，各安排一天就可以了！（笑）冠佑【Dr.】

真的很高兴可以登上一直期待的日本武道馆办演唱会。
而连续两天的两场演出，庆功宴会场可以不必在沾麵与烧肉两者间做痛苦的抉择，各安排一天就可以了！（笑）真的很高兴可以登上一直期待的日本武道馆办演唱会。
而连续两天的两场演出，庆功宴会场可以不必在沾麵与烧肉两者间做痛苦的抉择，各安排一天就可以了！（笑）MING [Drums]

I am very happy to perform at the Nippon Budokan. I’ve been dreaming of this for a while. Also, because the concerts will be held for 2 days, I don’t have to suffer deciding between “Tsukemen (Dip Noodles)” and “Yakiniku (Japanese Barbecue)” for our after party LOLI am very happy to perform at the Nippon Budokan. I’ve been dreaming of this for a while. Also, because the concerts will be held for 2 days, I don’t have to suffer deciding between “Tsukemen (Dip Noodles)” and “Yakiniku (Japanese Barbecue)” for our after party LOLMING（冠佑）【Dr.】

예전부터 염원했던 일본 부도칸 콘서트를 이번에 설 수 있게 되어 매우 기쁘게 생각합니다. 그리고 이틀 연속 2Days공연이라서 뒤풀이 장소를 「츠케멘(つけ麺:국물에 면을 찍어 먹는 요리)」과 「야키니꾸(焼き肉:일본식 고기집)」중 어느 쪽을 골라야 할 지, 행복한 고민을 지금부터 해야 하는 것도 기쁘게 생각합니다. (웃음）예전부터 염원했던 일본 부도칸 콘서트를 이번에 설 수 있게 되어 매우 기쁘게 생각합니다. 그리고 이틀 연속 2Days공연이라서 뒤풀이 장소를 「츠케멘(つけ麺:국물에 면을 찍어 먹는 요리)」과 「야키니꾸(焼き肉:일본식 고기집)」중 어느 쪽을 골라야 할 지, 행복한 고민을 지금부터 해야 하는 것도 기쁘게 생각합니다. (웃음）公演詳細演唱會情報演唱会情报Show Details공연상세Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道館
～DO YOU EVER SHINE～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道館
～DO YOU EVER SHINE～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道馆
～DO YOU EVER SHINE～Mayday
“Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO”
at Nippon Budokan
～DO YOU EVER SHINE～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 일본 부도칸
～DO YOU EVER SHINE～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道館
～抱きしめて～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道館
～擁抱～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 日本武道馆
～拥抱～Mayday
“Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO”
at Nippon Budokan
～Dakishimete～Mayday
「Just Rock It 2015 TOKYO」
at 일본 부도칸
～Dakishimete～日程日期日期Show Dates일정2015年8月28日（金）2015年8月28日（五）2015年8月28日（五）Friday, August 28, 20152015년8월28일（금）2015年8月29日（土）2015年8月29日（六）2015年8月29日（六）Saturday, August 29, 20152015년8월29일（토）会場會場会场Venue공연장日本武道館日本武道館日本武道馆Nippon Budokan일본 부도칸開場・開演觀眾進場／開演观眾进场／开演Door Opens / Show StartsOPEN ／ START18:00 開場 ／ 19:00 開演18:00觀眾進場／ 19:00開演18:00观眾进场／ 19:00开演Door Opens at 6PM / Show Starts at 7PM18:00 OPEN ／ 19:00 START16:00 開場 ／ 17:00 開演16:00觀眾進場／ 17:00開演16:00观眾进场／ 17:00开演Door Opens at 4PM / Show Starts at 5PM16:00 OPEN ／ 17:00 STARTチケット料金票價票价Ticket Price티켓가격指定席 ￥8,500（税込）
※3歳以上チケット必要 ／ 枚数制限6枚指定席 ￥8,500（含稅）
※3歳以上需購票指定席 ￥8,500（含税）
※3歳以上需购票Assigned Seat 8,500 Japanese Yen (Tax included)
*3-year-old or older must have a ticket전지정석　8,500엔（세금포함）
※3세 이상 티켓 필요チケット
一般発売日2015年7月19日（日）プレイガイドイープラス
http://eplus.jp　PC･携帯共通

ローソンチケット
0570-00-6969 発売日初日特電（※通常番号も可）
0570-084-003 （Lコード:76687）

チケットぴあ
0570-02-9900 発売日初日特電（※通常番号も可）
0570-02-9999 （Pコード:261-367） 主催主辦主办Organized by주최日本テレビ / TOKYO FM / DISK GARAGE日本電視放送網株式會社 / TOKYO FM / DISK GARAGE日本电视放送网株式会社 / TOKYO FM / DISK GARAGENippon Television Network Corporation / TOKYO FM / DISK GARAGENippon Television Network Corporation / TOKYO FM / DISK GARAGE企画企劃企划Planned by기획Amuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSIC制作製作製作Produced by제작Amuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSICAmuse / B'in MUSIC協賛贊助赞助Sponsored by협찬KKBOX / HTC / CHINA AIRLINESKKBOX / HTC / CHINA AIRLINESKKBOX / HTC / CHINA AIRLINESKKBOX / HTC / CHINA AIRLINESKKBOX / HTC / CHINA AIRLINES後援後援后援Supported by후원A-SketchA-SketchA-SketchA-SketchA-Sketch制作協力製作協力製作协力Co-produced by제작 협력Intergroove ProductionsIntergroove ProductionsIntergroove ProductionsIntergroove ProductionsIntergroove Productionsお問い合わせDISK GARAGE：050-5533-0888（平日12:00～19:00） ※車椅子にてご来場のお客様は事前にご連絡ください。
※客席を含む会場内の映像写真が公開されることがありますので予めご了承ください。
※営利目的での転売行為一切禁止/転売チケット入場不可※以輪椅來場的觀眾還請先行告知
※會場內含觀眾席部分的影像有攝影播放的可能性還請理解
※禁止一切以營利為目的所進行的票券轉賣行為／轉賣票券禁止入場※以轮椅来场的观眾还请先行告知
※会场内含观眾席部分的影像有摄影播放的可能性还请理解
※禁止一切以营利為目的所进行的票券转卖行為／转卖票券禁止入场*Please contact the organizer in advance if you attend in a wheelchair.
*Please note that videos and images of the shows including audiences might be released to public.
*Resale of tickets and admission with those tickets are prohibited. ※휠체어로 입장하실 고객분은 사전에 문의 해 주세요.
※객석을 포함 공연장의 영상,사진이 공개 될수 있으므로 양해 바랍니다.
※영리 목적으로 전매 행위는 절대 금지 / 재매 티켓 입장 불가機材席開放・チケット追加発売受付終了いたしました。たくさんのご応募ありがとうございました。 現在可以在樂天tickets買到五月天的門票 现在可以在乐天Tickets买到五月天的门票 Mayday tickets are now available via Rakuten Tickets 라쿠텐 티켓을 통해 메이데이 티켓을 구입 할 수 있습니다因為申請的張數眾多，門票已經完售。感謝大家踴躍的購買。因為申请的张数眾多，门票已经完售。感谢大家踊跃的购买。We have reached the allotted tickets for Rakuten ticket board and they are no longer available.
Thank you for contacting us.예정된 티켓수량에 도달하여 티켓예약이 종료되었습니다.
여러분의 많은 응모 해 주셔서 감사합니다. 現在可以在via ticket board買到五月天的門票 现在可以在via ticket board买到五月天的门票 Mayday tickets are now available via ticket board 티켓 보드를 통해 메이데이 티켓을 구입 할 수 있습니다因為申請的張數眾多，門票已經完售。感謝大家踴躍的購買。因為申请的张数眾多，门票已经完售。感谢大家踊跃的购买。We have reached the allotted tickets for Rakuten ticket board and they are no longer available.
Thank you for contacting us.예정된 티켓수량에 도달하여 티켓예약이 종료되었습니다.
여러분의 많은 응모 해 주셔서 감사합니다.チケット一般発売情報 受付終了いたしました。たくさんのご応募ありがとうございました。 国内外からのオフィシャルツアー受付
 (チケット＆オリジナルグッズ付)  國內外的官方Tour申請
（附演唱會門票及特製明星商品）  国内外的官方Tour申请
（附演唱会门票及特製明星商品）  Official Travel tour from overseas and within Japan
(A show ticket and original goods included)  국내외에서 공식 투어 접수
(티켓 & 오리지널 굿즈 포함) 受付終了いたしました。
当落確認・入金期間についてはツアー詳細にてご確認下さいませ。已經截止。關於抽選結果，匯款期限等情報請於Tour詳細內容部分確認。已经截止。关於抽选结果，匯款期限等情报请於Tour详细内容部分确认。Time limit for application expired.
Please refer to the “tour details” for next procedure접수 종료했습니다. 당첨 확인 · 입금 기간은 투어 상세내용에서 확인해 주시기 바랍니다.＜ 海外 ＞
上海・北京・広州・香港発着のツアーを実施！預定實施
上海・北京・廣州・香港出發的tour!预定实施
上海・北京・广州・香港出发的tour!＜Overseas＞
There will be travel tours from/to Shanghai, Beijing, Guangzhou, and Hong Kong!＜해외＞
상하이/베이징/홍콩 ⇔ 도쿄 왕복 투어 실시! ツアー詳細はこちら！ Tour的詳細內容請看這裡！ Tour的详细内容请看这裡！ Click here for tour details! 투어에 대한 상세 내용은 여기를 확인하세요！※台湾発着のオフィシャルツアーに関しては、
China Airlines Website をご確認下さい。※自台灣出發的官方tour，請參閱China Airlines Website。※自台湾出发的官方tour，请参阅China Airlines Website。*For the official travel tour from/to Taiwan, please visit China Airlines Website.※대만 왕복의 공식 투어에 관해서는 China Airlines Website를 확인 해 주세요.＜ 日本 ＞
札幌・名古屋・大阪・福岡等発着のツアーを実施！札幌・名古屋・大阪・福岡等発着のツアーを実施！預定將實施
札幌・名古屋・大阪・福岡出發的tour！札幌・名古屋・大阪・福岡出發的tour！预定将实施
札幌・名古屋・大阪・福冈出发的tour！札幌・名古屋・大阪・福冈出发的tour！＜Japan＞
There will be tours from Sapporo, Nagoya, Osaka, Fukuoka and other cities!There will be tours from Sapporo, Nagoya, Osaka, Fukuoka and other cities!＜일본＞
삿포로(札幌)·나고야(名古屋)·오사카(大阪)·후쿠오카(福岡) 등 출발 투어를 실시!삿포로(札幌)·나고야(名古屋)·오사카(大阪)·후쿠오카(福岡) 등 출발 투어를 실시! ツアー詳細はこちら！ Tour的詳細內容請看這裡！ Tour的详细内容请看这裡！ Click here for tour details! 투어에 대한 상세 내용은 여기를 확인하세요！※海外から各エリアにご到着の際も、ご利用頂けます。
※催行人数に満たない場合はプランの実施を見合わせる場合がございます。あらかじめご了承くださいませ。※來自海外到達各地的觀眾也可利用。
※申請人數未達最低限額時有可能視情況調整方案的實施。敬請見諒。※来自海外到达各地的观眾也可利用。
※申请人数未达最低限额时有可能视情况调整方案的实施。敬请见谅。*also available for the fans from overseas.
※Please note that if we do not reach the minimum number of participants, the plan may be cancelled.※해외에서 상기 일본 지역에 도착 후, 도쿄로 왕복 이용도 가능합니다.
※투어 개최 인원수에 못 미칠 경우 플랜의 실시를 보류할 경우가 있습니다. 미리 양해 해주시기 바랍니다."
